{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Concrete Repair \u0026 Resurface Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40016/":{"taskOID":40016,"originalTaskOID":40016,"setID":340,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7042,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Repair/Resurface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the location of the concrete repair/resurface project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10525,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Finish floor in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Finish floor in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10526,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Subflooring in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Subflooring in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10527,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage or basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage or basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10528,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10529,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exterior walkway/patio","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway/patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10530,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10531,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10532,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Pool Deck","answerDisplayText":"Pool Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4061,"questionDisplayText":"Damage Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the damage to your concrete?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2973,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Heaving or settling","answerDisplayText":"Heaving or settling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1938,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Dirty or stained","answerDisplayText":"Dirty or stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1696,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cracked or chipped","answerDisplayText":"Cracked or chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2143,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Edge is cracked or broken","answerDisplayText":"Edge is cracked or broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2502,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flaking","answerDisplayText":"Flaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2121,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Dusty","answerDisplayText":"Dusty","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7042,"questionDisplayText":"Location of Repair/Resurface","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the location of the concrete repair/resurface project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10525,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Finish floor in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Finish floor in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10526,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Subflooring in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Subflooring in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10527,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage or basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage or basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10528,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10529,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exterior walkway/patio","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway/patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10530,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10531,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10532,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Pool Deck","answerDisplayText":"Pool Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10525,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Finish floor in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Finish floor in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10526,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Subflooring in a living space","answerDisplayText":"Subflooring in a living space","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10527,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage or basement floor","answerDisplayText":"Garage or basement floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10528,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Driveway/parking area","answerDisplayText":"Driveway/parking area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10529,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Exterior walkway/patio","answerDisplayText":"Exterior walkway/patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10530,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pad for a light structure","answerDisplayText":"Pad for a light structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10531,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Steps","answerDisplayText":"Steps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10532,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Pool Deck","answerDisplayText":"Pool Deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4061,"questionDisplayText":"Damage Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the damage to your concrete?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2973,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Heaving or settling","answerDisplayText":"Heaving or settling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1938,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Dirty or stained","answerDisplayText":"Dirty or stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1696,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cracked or chipped","answerDisplayText":"Cracked or chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2143,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Edge is cracked or broken","answerDisplayText":"Edge is cracked or broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2502,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flaking","answerDisplayText":"Flaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2121,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Dusty","answerDisplayText":"Dusty","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2973,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Heaving or settling","answerDisplayText":"Heaving or settling","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1938,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Dirty or stained","answerDisplayText":"Dirty or stained","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1696,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Cracked or chipped","answerDisplayText":"Cracked or chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2143,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Edge is cracked or broken","answerDisplayText":"Edge is cracked or broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2502,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Flaking","answerDisplayText":"Flaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2121,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Dusty","answerDisplayText":"Dusty","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40016/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40016,"taskName":"Concrete Flatwork - Repair \u0026 Resurface","taskDescription":"Repair or Resurface Concrete Driveways, Patios, Walks \u0026 Floors","xmTaskDescriptor":"Concrete Repair \u0026 Resurface Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":287,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"concrete driveway floor patio walkway","textMessagingName":"Repr Concrete Flat","rolloverLongDesc":"Provides a temporary solution to cracked or broken concrete. Many firms will not do this because consumers have unrealistic expectations about how long the repair will last.  For permanent repairs, the concrete has to be completely replaced.","rolloverShortDesc":"Patch, repair, or resurface holes or cracks in flat concrete.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair and Resurface Concrete Driveways, Patios, Walks \u0026 Floors.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Concrete Resurfacing | Repair a Concrete Surface \u003cin_city\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Concrete Flatwork Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Concrete Flatwork - Repair \u0026 Resurface","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Concrete Flatwork Repair Project","urlName":"Concrete-Flatwork-for-Driveways-Floors-etc-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Concrete Repair \u0026 Resurfacers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"concrete,driveway,floor,patio,walkway,sidwalk,resurface","emcCategoryOid":-12015,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":340,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}